[
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of France?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Feingold Diet used to treat Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) in children eliminates:",
        "answer": "Artificial food colorings, additives, and preservatives"
    },
    {
        "question": "The DASH diet is often used to treat:",
        "answer": "Hypertension"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which test(s) are most useful for evaluating long term blood sugar control in diabetics?",
        "answer": "HbAle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which managerial technique is most likely to improve employee morale?",
        "answer": "Use of employee self-assessment during performance reviews"
    },
    {
        "question": "Problems encountered in delivering nutrition services to migrant populations include:",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is true for reactive hypoglycemia?",
        "answer": "It is treated with a diet high in complex carbohydrates."
    },
    {
        "question": "Intake of fermented foods and aged cheeses needs to be avoided in individuals taking monoamine oxidase inhibitors (MAO inhibitors) because of:",
        "answer": "Potential interaction between epinephrine and pressor amines"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not advised for preventing dental caries in children less than 12 months of age?",
        "answer": "A. Use of prescription fluoride supplements"
    },
    {
        "question": "ip code here. ything other than requested test results and question of the day emails. Lastname Optional fe the US",
        "answer": "ip"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the order point of stewed tomatoes if 3 cases are used each day, 5 cases are needed as safety stock, and 7 days are needed for delivery from the time an order is placed?",
        "answer": "26 cases"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hyperemesis gravidarum may be treated with:",
        "answer": "A&B"
    },
    {
        "question": "During disaster planning a consulting RD be asked to participate in which of the following activities:",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ounces are in a size 24 serving scoop?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "A pregnant woman with a pre-pregnancy BMI of 27 has gained 22 pounds in the second trimester. What recommendation should the registered dietitian provide to her concerning additional weight gain?",
        "answer": "5 pounds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sennen",
        "answer": "naan"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ounces are in a size 24 serving scoop?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which managerial technique is most likely to improve employee morale?",
        "answer": "Use of employee self-assessment during performance reviews"
    }
]